Johnny Otis Collection, 1949-2012 SC 106
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 4. Radio Airchecks, Johnny Otis Show
  - 4.2. KPFK (Los Angeles) and KPFA (Berkeley), 1982-1994
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Good Ol' Good Ones, 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Lonnie Mack, Miracles, Four Tops, Robert & Johnny, Marvin Gaye & Kim Weston, Jerry Butler, Brook Benton & Dinah Washington, Billy Stewart, Shirelles, Dee Clark, Fontella Bass, Chuck Berry, Marvelettes, Martha & The Vandellas, Lloyd Price, Ray Charles, Miracles, Coasters, Roger Collins, Jackie Wilson, Stevie Wonder, Johnny Watson & Larry Williams, Smokey Robinson & The Miracles, Marvin Gaye & Tammi Terrell, Jay & The Techniques, Junior Walker & The All-Stars, Peaches & Herb, Aretha Franklin, Lou Courtney, Sam & Bill, and Rufus Thomas. Remainder of reel is a different radio program.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Marv Johnson, Clovers, Falcons, Ray Charles, Coasters, Little Richard, Chuck Berry, Heartbeats, Buster Brown, El Dorados, Silhouettes, Moonglows, Contours, Cufflinks, Platters, Marvelettes, Larry Williams, Wilson Pickett, Rivingtons, Lloyd Price, Bobby Day, Mary Wells, Drifters, Marvin Gaye, and Five Satins. Remainder of reel is a different radio program.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1987?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.
      EC10 2670
      Related Materials
      Possibly belongs with EC10 2668-2669.
      Not yet digitized. Contents unknown.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1987?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.
      EC10 2671
      Possibly belongs with EC10 2672-2673.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1987?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.
      EC10 2672
      Possibly belongs with EC10 2671, EC10 2673.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.
      EC10 2681
- 5. Time-based Media
  - Johnny Otis Show, KTLA TV (episode of the weekly series), 2022-04-07; 1 Videocassette VHS
    VC 1172
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c08h446g6z
  - Johnny Otis with IU Soul Revue, Bloomington Convention Center, SEM Conference (back camera), 1998-10-24; 1 Videocassette VHS
    VC 1173
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s55m317f2r
  - Johnny Otis with IU Soul Revue, Bloomington Convention Center, SEM Conference (close-up camera), 1998-10-24; 1 Videocassette VHS
    VC 1174
  - Johnny Otis with IU Soul Revue, Bloomington Convention Center, SEM Conference, 1998-10-24; 2 Videocassettes MDV
    MDV 243; MDV 244
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k61r46z445
  - Johnny Otis with IU Soul Revue, Bloomington Convention Center, SEM Conference, 1998-10-24; 2 Audiocassettes DAT
    DAT 2; DAT 3
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/969z012868
  - Johnny Otis Forum, SEM Conference, Bloomington, IN, 1998-10-24; 2 Videocassettes MDV
    MDV 241; MDV 242
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/752633mg74
  - Johnny Otis Interview, SEM Conference, Bloomington, IN, 1998-10-25; 1 Videocassette MDV
    MDV 245
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/475247mb3k
  - Photograph identification interview with Johnny Otis conducted by Portia Maultsby, 2010-11-12; 1 Digital File
    DAF 26
    https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/900n79j680
- 6. Photographs
  - George Washington with trombone, in profile, 1958-03; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005502
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000001
  - Ernie Andrews standing on stage with microphone, 1958-04; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005503
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000002
  - Roosevelt Miles, leader of the West Coast Drifters, singing on stage, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005504
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000003
  - Louis Jordan and Little Arthur Matthews playing saxophones on stage, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005505
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000004
  - Johnny Otis and Bardu Ali standing together in front of car, 1958; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005506
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000005
  - Little Esther Phillips and the Jayos singing on stage, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005507
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000006
  - Johnny Otis onstage with The Rivingtons performing background vocals, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005508
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000007
  - Three Tons of Joy standing on steps of tour bus, 1957; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005509
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000008
  - Mel Walker, Johnny Otis, Little Esther, and Don Johnson on stage, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005510
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000009
  - Johnny Otis seated at KWBR mic holding Mambo record, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005511
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000010
  - Louis Jordan and unidentified vocalist performing on stage, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005512
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000011
  - Louis Jordan singing into mic, pointing with index finger, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005513
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000012
  - Johnny Otis speaking to California politician Mervin Dymally in building lobby, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005514
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000013
  - Mel Williams close-up at microphone, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005515
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000014
  - Johnny Otis on stage with Etta James and Richard Berry, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005516
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000015
  - Little Arthur Matthews at microphone with audience in background, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005517
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000016
  - Louis Jordan at mic with unidentified female vocalist, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005518
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000017
  - Louis Jordan action close-up, singing into mic, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005519
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000018
  - Trombonist George Washington head and shoulders portrait, 1958-03; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005520
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000019
  - Slappy White, Johnny Otis and unidentified man standing in front of brick building, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005521
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000020
  - Fred Harmon in striped tuxedo jacket playing saxophone, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005522
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000021
  - Ernie Andrews singing into microphone, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005523
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000022
  - Johnny Otis at drumset performing with saxophonist Louis Jordan, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005524
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000023
  - Johnny Otis with singer Marti Barris, posing in front of KTLA television camera, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005525
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000024
  - Johnny Otis seated at turntable in front of KFOX microphone, 1960; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005526
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000025
  - Louis Jordan standing at microphone and holding saxophone, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005527
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000026
  - Three Tons of Joy with Johnny Otis, the Otisettes, and the Johnny Otis Show band. Otis Show logo, 3 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005528
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000027
  - Three Tons of Joy with Johnny Otis on stage under striped awning with Johnny Otis Show band, 2 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005529
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000028
  - Johnny Otis driving horse drawn wagon carrying the Three Tons of Joy, 1957; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005530
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000029
  - George Washington in white tuxedo playing trombone, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005531
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000030
  - Louis Jordan and Little Arthur Matthews playing saxophones on stage, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005532
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000031
  - Willa Dorsey, wearing church choir robe, singing in front of curtain, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005533
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000032
  - Johnny Otis, Tom Morgan and Bardu Ali having coffee at Capitol Records, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005534
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000033
  - Jim Coates, Frank Gallo, and Johnny Otis in the studio with KTTV cameraman, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005535
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000034
  - Johnny Otis at Jordan High School in Watts with members of the Rock and Roll Fan Club, 1957; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005536
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000035
  - Mel Williams in tux, formal portrait, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005537
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000036
  - Johnny Otis on stage addressing audience at a NAACP meeting, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005538
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000037
  - Johnny Otis and Mel Williams on stage with microphone and striped curtains, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005539
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000038
  - Johnny Otis posing with the Everly Brothers, who are holding their guitars, 1960; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005540
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000039
  - Johnny Otis, Esther Phillips, and band members seated around a table, 1960; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005541
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000040
  - Johnny Otis seated behind desk talking to Marie Adams, 1960; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005542
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000041
  - Johnny Otis and Little Arthur Matthews on stage with microphone, band and striped curtains in background, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005543
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000042
  - Redd Lyte publicity portrait, 1950; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005544
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000043
  - Johnny Otis Show performing for television, Metropolitan Ford logo on podium, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005545
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000044
  - Johnny Otis playing vibes with members of his band in background, 3 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005546
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000045
  - Johnny Otis with Willie Bryant (aka "Mayor of Harlem") in KALI radio studio in Pasadena, 1960; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005547
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000046
  - Johnny Otis in short sleeve shirt seated at KFOX console, 1960; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005548
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000047
  - Johnny Otis standing next to B.B. King, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005549
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000048
  - Johnny Otis standing behind Three Tons of Joy, Arthur Matthews laying down on stage, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005550
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000049
  - Johnny Otis on stage with arm around Louis Jordan, who is holding saxophone, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005551
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000050
  - Johnny Otis plugging his ears while Marie Adams plays vibes, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005552
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000051
  - Johnny Otis in foreground introducing the Penguins, striped curtains and Otis band in background, 2 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005553
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000052
  - Johnny Otis with Louis Jordan, who is playing saxophone, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005554
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000053
  - Tom Morgan and Johnny Otis posing in studio holding beer bottles, 1960; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005555
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000054
  - The Moonbeams posing for group portrait on the set of the Johnny Otis Show television program, 1959; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005556
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000055
  - Johnny Otis portrait in front of KWBR microphone, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005557
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000056
  - Sallie Blair publicity portrait, wearing ruffled strapless gowngown, 1960; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005558
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000057
  - Johnny Otis seated in KFOX studio with young Shuggie Otis in his lap holding 45 rpm record, 1957; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005559
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000058
  - Johnny Otis seated at grand piano, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005560
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000059
  - Johnny Otis surrounded by children with hula hoops on his TV show, 1960; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005561
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000060
  - Mel Williams head and shoulders portrait, wearing jacket and tie, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005562
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000061
  - Tom Bradley standing by Johnny Otis, who is reading letter; campaign banners in background, 1963; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005563
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000062
  - Willie Bryant posing with Johnny Otis in a record store, holding up record albums, 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005564
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000063
  - Johnny Otis playing piano, publicity portrait, 1980; 4 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005565
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000064
  - Johnny Otis Band standing around grand piano, 1980; 2 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.; 1 negative b&w; 3 x 5 in.
    PA005566
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000065
  - Johnny Otis seated at piano with microphone and saxophone, 1980; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005567
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000066
  - Johnny Otis leaving the Capitol Records Building at 1750 Vine Street, 1960; 2 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005568
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000067
  - Johnny Otis leaving the Capitol Tower building, Johnny Otis leaving the Capitol Records Building at 1750 Vine Street wearing rain coatwearing suit and rain coat (slightly different from PA5568), 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005568.1
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000068
  - Johnny Otis with sons Shuggie and Nick and unidentified guitarist under Pure Organic Apple Juice sign, 1994-02; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005569
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000069
  - Johnny Otis holding up Burgie sign with (Irving Burgie?) seated at organ, 1950-1959; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005570
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000070
  - Unidentified artist (Mel Williams?) publicity portrait, 1950-1959; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005571
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000071
  - Johnny Otis with Louis Jordan playing sax, KTLA camera in background, 1950-1959; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005572
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000072
  - Johnny Otis and The Otisettes, 1966; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005573
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000073
  - Johnny Otis and band at rehearsal in club, 1950-1959; 2 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005574
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000074
  - Johnny Otis standing outside the Crescendo under marquee "Gene Norman Presents Johnny Otis Show", 1950-1959; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005575
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000075
  - Johnny Otis, Tom Morgan, Bardu Ali having coffee at Capitol Records' studio, 1950-1959; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005576
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000076
  - Johnny Otis on set with panel of musicians and teenagers (on his television show?), 1960-1969; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005577
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000077
  - Johnny Otis in TV studio by projection unit with two unidentified black males, 1955-1960; 2 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005578
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000078
  - Johnny Otis in TV studio with two unidentified black males, one demonstrating control panel, 1955-1960; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005579
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000079
  - Johnny Otis in TV studio with two unidentified black males, one seated at console, 1955-1960; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005580
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000080
  - Johnny Otis in TV studio with two unidentified black men, pointing to equipment with RCA Color Television logo, 1955-1960; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005581
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000081
  - Skillet and Leroy, publicity photo, 1950-1959; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005582
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000082
  - Gene and Billy (a.k.a. Gene Ford and Billy Boyd) in recording studio singing into microphone, 1955; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005583
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000083
  - Johnny Otis carrying Arthur Matthews on his back with guitar and luggage, being pulled on a leash by the Three Tons of Joy, 1957; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005584
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000084
  - Johnny Otis speaking at panel "Save Fair Housing, Save Pay T-V", six men seated in background, 1960-1969; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005585
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000085
  - Johnny Otis speaking at panel "Save Fair Housing, Save Pay T-V", two men seated in background, 1960-1969; 2 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005586
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000086
  - Johnny Otis speaking at panel "Save Fair Housing, Save Pay T-V", four men seated in background, 1960-1969; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005587
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000087
  - Johnny Otis posing with panelists, all clasping hands, at "Save Fair Housing" meeting, 1960-1969; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005588
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000088
  - Johnny Otis on drums, with Count Otis Matthews and West Oakland Houserockers (p.54 bio.), 1940; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005589
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000089
  - Johnny Otis on drums in background with West Oakland Houserockers, trumpeter in foreground, 1940; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005590
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000090
  - Johnny Otis on stage conducting the Johnny Otis Band, 1950-1959; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005591
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000091
  - Johnny Otis with Rubén Guevara, holding up album covers for History of Latino Rock, vol. 1 and Los Angelinos, 1983; 1 Photograph b&w; 3.5 x 4 in.
    PA005592
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000092
  - Johnny Otis in church preaching from pulpit, with band, choir, and congregation (Landmark Community Church?), 1970-1979; 1 Photograph color; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005593
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000093
  - Vacant building by parking lot and billiard hall, 1963-02; 1 Photograph b&w; 3.5 x 5 in.
    PA005594
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000094
  - Johnny Otis standing with black woman [vocalist?] and [Little Matthew?], surrounded by band members, 1950-1959; 1 Photograph b&w; 4 x 10 in.
    PA005595
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000095
  - Johnny Otis wearing tweed jacket, arms crossed, standing in front of stucco wall, 1958-05; 1 Photograph b&w; 5 x 7 in.
    PA005596
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000096
  - Unidentified man standing by KTLA Television camera, 1945; 1 Photograph b&w; 4 x 8.5 in.
    PA005597
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000097
  - Johnny Otis Show at Big 10 Ballroom in Tulsa, audience in foreground, 1950-1959; 1 Photograph b&w; 4 x 5 in.
    PA005598
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000098
  - Johnny Otis publicity portrait for "The Johnny Otis Show," music staff in background, 1980-1989; 2 photographs b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA005599
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000099
  - Johnny Otis (in captain hat) with five unidentified people boarding a Pacific Southwest Airlines flight at San Fransisco International Airport, 1955; 1 Photograph b&w; 3 x 5 in.; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005600
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000100
  - Johnny Otis (in captain hat) boarding a Southwest flight, 1955; 1 Photograph b&w; 3 x 5 in.; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005601
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000101
  - Johnny Otis (in cardigan sweater) with two unidentified men boarding bus, 1955; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005602
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000102
  - Johnny Otis (in cardigan sweater) with two unidentified men boarding bus, 1955; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005603
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000103
  - Two unidentified men outside of San Francisco Airport bus, one with cigar, 1955; 1 Photograph b&w; 3 x 5 in.; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005604
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000104
  - Two unidentified men outside of bus, one with cigar, 1955; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005605
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000105
  - Three unidentified men on the steps of a bus, one with drink in hand, 1955; 1 Photograph b&w; 3 x 5 in.; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005606
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000106
  - Three Tons of Joy on the steps of a bus, 1955; 1 negative b&w; 35 mm.
    PA005607
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD9211/VAD9211-000107